#### Contact

968482693 (Mobile) cmonteiro67@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/carlos-monteiro-74599a (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Account Management
Project Management
Program Management

# **Carlos Monteiro**

Procura de Novo Desafio Profissional | Em busca de novos desafios! Lisbon Area, Portugal

### Summary

IT Professional with experience in Account/Client Management, Team and Project Management in many sectors, including Telecom, Public Administration, Banking / Finance, "Utilities", Distribution and Production Industries. I have developed multiple functions Management Multidisciplinary Teams and Multicultural Management, Programs and Projects with high complexity and incorporation of multiple technologies and management methodologies.

## Experience

Em busca de novos desafios! Procura de Novo Desafio Profissional February 2020 - Present (4 months) Lisboa e Região

Sage Portugal
Portugal Services Manager
June 2015 - February 2020 (4 years 9 months)

Meta4 Director Comercial May 2014 - June 2015 (1 year 2 months) Lisbon Area, Portugal

Ahnfelt Consultants
Project Manager
August 2013 - February 2014 (7 months)

Hewlett-Packard Client/Project Manager February 2005 - June 2013 (8 years 5 months) Lisbon Area, Portugal

KPMG Management Consulting

Manager January 1996 - January 2005 (9 years 1 month) Lisboa

Prodstar Consultor January 1994 - December 1995 (2 years)

Ipetex, SA Responsável Departamento Logística June 1991 - December 1993 (2 years 7 months) Cartaxo

#### Education

Faculdade de Ciências e Tecnologia da UNL Licenciatura, Engenharia de Produção Industrial · (1985 - 1990)